WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
www.tvsubtitles.net
Y a même pas un an
on se mariait au Canada.
Et aujourd'hui on est en train
de se battre pour nos droits
Et ça grâce cet enculé
de la Maison Blanche
Tu sais que tu parles de plus en plus
comme ta mère?
Tu sais dans le temps
je t'aurais dit "j't'emmerde"
mais aujourd'hui je prend ça comme un compliment
Non mais franchement, qui peut voir ça
comme une abomination?
Plein de monde Debbie, la plupart des gens.
Ouais, ben ils ont tord.
Et y compris cet enculé
à la Maison Blanche.
And that includes that asshole
in the White House.
Every time I read about
a gay minister being defrocked
or a gay couple having their kids
taken away from them,
it just fucking breaks my heart.
Protect
the family! Protect our children!
Protect Christian values!
Vote yes on 14.
Vote yes!
Stop the homosexual agenda.
Protect our children!
Vote yes on 14.
Yes on 14. Yes on 14.
Protect our children.
Vote yes on 14.
Stop the homosexual agenda.
Jesus forgives sinners.
Vote yes on 14.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I've got news for you -
Jesus thinks you stink!
Protect our children.
Protect Christian values!
Vote yes on 14.
What a fabulous event
this is going to be.
If the planner does say so himself.
Now, how many tickets have we sold?
Over 300.
And counting.
At $200 a pop, that's over $60,000.
That doesn't even include what we'll
make during the silent auction.
Not bad for a night's work.
Now, if I could just get Drew
to attend.
Think of the media attention
we'd get. You can't buy that.
Well, like my Aunt Lil always said -
"They can't shoot you for asking."
Roy.
I would like you to meet
my planning committee and friends.
Ben.
Hi.
Michael. Emmett.
How do you do?
This is Roy Harris,
the hotel manager.
He's been terrific, so helpful.
Thanks for cutting us
such a great deal.
Don't thank me just yet.
I'm afraid I have bad news.
Corporate just called. They're not
going to let you hold the event here.
Excuse me?!
What?
Why'd they change their minds?
That's privileged information.
Considering you just tanked
our event,
I think we deserve the privilege
of an explanation.
Let's just say there's a couple
of very large accounts
corporate's afraid of alienating.
By having an event they might
be perceived as gay-friendly.
Look, I support
what you're doing 100%.
I've been in a relationship
for 15 years. I want to protect that.
But I also have to protect my job.
I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah. He's hot.
Schmidt.
What did I tell you about playing
with yourself during office hours?
Fuck, Brian.
Relax, Theodore.
This isn't work shafters.
You're in a jerk-off-friendly
environment.
I wasn't jerking off.
I'm on my quest for a husband.
The latest homo to join
the rank of defectors.
So, who's the stiff?
And I don't mean that
in the best sense of the word.
As you know,
I lost my Jewish doctor,
so I decided to try
husbandmaterial.com.
It's a website that's full
of quality guys, like myself,
who are looking
for the perfect partner.
So... ..what treasures
have you uncovered online?
Well, this is Richard. He's 36.
He's a lawyer, he owns his own house
and he likes to cuddle
after a long day.
Uh...oh, this is James. 35.
He's a dentist.
And he likes... ..well, to cuddle after a long day.
Uh... Oh. This... Lewis. He's 37.
He owns his own business
and he likes...
He likes to cuddle after a long day.
..to cuddle after a long day.
Doesn't anyone like to fuck?
Let's see some cock shots.
There are no cock shots.
Well, then how do you know
if they're quality men?
Move over.
This is Roland. He's 32.
He doesn't have time for a career.
He likes to cuddle
after being pounded into oblivion.
Too bad for you he's in Australia.
Not really, since I plan
on being there in less than 48 hours.
I just got back from the doctor.
I got a clean bill of health.
I'm completely cancer-free.
That's great news!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, to celebrate, I'm going to go
to Gay Mardi Gras in Sydney.
I wish I could go.
What?! You've got to find a hubby.
G'day, mate.
Smells good.
I felt like cooking.
You ran out this morning.
I didn't run out.
I had a meeting at the hotel.
How did it go?
They told us
to find some place else.
What?
We have to find another venue.
Well, it's a little late for that,
isn't it?
I'm going to go take a shower.
Mel.
Look...I glued it back together.
If you turn it like this,
you can hardly notice the cracks.
Are we just going to pretend
as if it never happened?
No-one's pretending.
In fact, I hear it happens
to a lot of divorced couples.
Some say the sex is even hotter
than when they're married.
It was a mistake.
A...momentary lapse in judgment.
Just one of those 'in the heat
of the moment' sort of things.
Precisely.
Then I guess we should disregard it.
Move on.
I think that would be best.
Deb, did you ever date
a younger man?
Sunshine,
until Karl came along,
I was barely dating a living one.
But if you'd had the chance?
I'd have jumped on it.
Which is what I hope
your mother's doing.
Yeah, but he's half her age.
Jeez. You kids - you don't cut
your parents much slack, do you?
Well, under the sexual
bill of rights -
that is, if we still
have any rights -
she's entitled to the same freedoms
you and Brian have.
Had.
You catch my drift.
Fucking pepper.
I've done my share
of running around,
but...when I read your description -
enjoy spending quiet evenings
at home -
there's something about it
I found very appealing.
To tell you the truth,
I...I've never liked going out much.
See, when I was a kid, the Partridge
Family reunion came to town,
and, uh... 304
and, uh... 305
..I wanted
Danny Bonaduce's autograph so bad.
So, I waited in line for four hours,
and then finally, there they were,
dressed in those white jumpsuits.
Oh, God, I remember those.
David Cassidy - I had such a crush.
Anyway, there was a stampede.
I got trampled.
That's terrible.
Yeah, it was pretty terrifying.
In fact, I still get nervous
being in a crowd.
So, how's the date going?
It is not a date, Deb.
We're just getting acquainted.
Ah. Are we checking each other out
to make sure you're not trolls?
And then you go and fuck? Huh?
Yeah. Deb has a way of cutting
right to the chase.
So, have we, uh...
officially passed the troll test?
Yeah.
Well, how about a real date?
Great.
I just bought two tickets to the
Stop Prop 14 benefit Thursday night.
Cyndi Lauper's performing.
I...I'd love to, but...
Crowds. Right.
Um...well, some other time.
No. No, wait.
My therapist says it's important
I stare down my demons,
so...that's what I'm going to do.
You sure?
It's a date.
Great.
Uh, 300, maybe as many as 400.
For this Thursday night.
Yes, I know, it's a big crowd.
Yeah, I know it's short notice.
Whatever it takes to make it work.
Saturday won't work.
Are you sure you can't...
There's no way that you can...
Well, thanks.
Thanks anyway.
No luck?
Nada.
Same here.
So, who's left?
That's it. Everything's either booked
or they don't want us.
This is a disaster.
There's one place.
I'm not asking him for anything.
Michael, this is important.
Can't you and Brian put aside
your differences for one night?
I'm sorry. I'm not going to do it.
Well, then, I guess
we'll just have to call the centre,
tell them the benefit's off.
You've got to try the Bodyline.
The best bathhouse in Sydney.
Bodyline.
That's it, mate.
Fuck me. Harder!
What about clubs?
I prefer Arq on Oxford.
Friendly. Young crowd.
Arq on Oxford.
The midnight shift's packed
on the weekends.
Oh, yeah.
Don't stop. I'm close.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, mate. Oh, yes. Yes.
Oh, yes! Oh...
Shit.
Oh...
Jeez. I was calling and calling.
Why didn't you just buy a stick
of dynamite and blast the door down?
It's the Brown Athletics account...
Oops...sorry.
Not as sorry as he is.
What about it?!
Leo Brown just heard
about Drew Boyd.
He wants another spokesman
for his underwear line.
Did you tell him that
we've already booked the photoshoot?
That the ad space
has already been paid for?
He said, "That's your problem.
"But if you don't find someone else,
you'll have a bigger one."
Bottom line - a gay player
is disruptive to a team.
Imagine that you're in
a locker room...
Don't tell me his team-mates
are afraid he'll jump them.
Those big guys
can't take care of themselves? No.
Besides, he didn't chase them
around the showers before.
Why would he now?
By announcing that he was gay,
Drew Boyd has separated himself
from the rest of the team.
The spirit of unity, the playing
together as one, has been broken
and it can never be repaired.
So, you're saying
they should get rid of him?
If he was on my team, I would.
I'd say I had no choice...
Hey, I was watching that.
Why?
So you can get even more depressed?
I have just the thing
to take your mind off it.
'Madame X'.
Starring the unjustly
underrated Lana Turner.
What a performance.
Lana has an illicit affair,
and after being discovered, is forced
to forfeit her identity as her.
She wanders the world
in a drunken stupor,
finally to return home
and murder her blackmailer.
And this is supposed
to make me feel better?
Yeah, well,
Lana always does it for me.
Hey, you know what really
might make you feel better?
Coming with me
to the Stop Prop 14 event.
You can meet your gay fans,
see what a role model
and inspiration you've become.
I told you -
I'm a professional football player,
not a professional fag!
So stop trying to get me to be
the new gay poster boy!
You'd better take care of yourself.
You've got a near-naked photoshoot
coming up.
There's not going to be
a photoshoot.
Your friend Kinney called.
He fired me.
Brian fired you?
I've now officially lost everything.
I knew it wouldn't be easy
coming out,
but I never expected
it would be this bad.
You haven't lost me.
We'll figure this out.
If you don't mind...
I need some time alone.
Sure. I understand.
It's freezing, huh?
Hey, we could go back to my place.
I'll warm you up.
It's kind of late and...
Corinne...
I know. You don't have to tell me.
No, it's not you, I swear.
I...I know that too.
It's Lindsay.
Hey, come on, you don't need
a special team of investigators
to figure out what's what.
Besides, it's not a crime.
Mind if I ask you what gave me away?
Penguins.
When my dad left my mom,
she was so obsessed,
you could mention any subject
and somehow she'd make it about him.
Penguins.
"Your father hated wearing
a tuxedo."
You're the same way.
Julia Roberts.
"Lindsay got her hair cut
like Julia Roberts."
The French hate Americans.
"Lindsay makes
a great bouillabaisse."
I didn't realise.
Well, why should you?
Referring to her is as automatic
to you as blinking.
Just...next time, be fair.
Until you can buy
a tube of toothpaste
and not mention
Lindsay's perfect smile...
..don't let some poor girl think
she's got a chance.
That's Andy Prather. He's the
running back for the Chargers.
Mmm. Definitely the hottest
of the hotties.
Check out those abs.
I have - about a thousand times.
Straight, right?
Yeah.
I have several teenage girls
who'll swear under oath
they've been raped by him.
Perfect. When can he be here?
Once you sign off,
he'll be on the next plane.
Book him.
Great.
Hey, Teddy.
Michael.
Wow. It's a...
..surprise to see you here.
Ri...right, Bri? Isn't it
a surprise to, uh...see him...here?
I'm speechless. Except to say that
if you and your guest will excuse me.
Actually, I'm here to see you.
Oh, I'll, uh...I'll...I'll just...
I'll take off
and leave you two
to do whatever you two need to do.
I won't waste too much of your time.
That's good. Because I don't have
too much to offer.
Then I'll get right to the point.
The point being, you want something?
Yes.
Wouldn't happen to be
to apologise, would it?
I believe it's you who owes me that.
I already offered. You refused.
Because you didn't mean
a goddamn word!
But that's not why you're here.
We lost La Montage for the benefit -
Stop Prop 14.
Yeah, I live in Pittsburgh.
I've heard of it.
It seems that some
of their very important clients
might object to us using it.
We've tried every place in town...
but they're all booked.
Every place except...
Babylon.
So, you want nothing
to do with my world
until, of course,
you need it to help yours.
This has nothing to do with my world
versus your world
versus your world,
but...you know, since it's
going to be a problem, forget it.
I didn't say you couldn't have it.
How much were you paying La Montage?
$10,000. We'll pay you the same.
No, you won't.
Look, there's no reason to gouge us
just because we're desperate.
We don't have it.
There's no charge.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Consider it my donation to the cause.
I don't know what to say.
Well, 'thanks'...will do.
Now, if you don't mind,
I have to get back to work
so that I can continue
my decadent lifestyle.
Cynthia, will you get me Leo Brown
on the phone, please?
Thanks.
Linz?
Linz?!
In here.
It's a lovely home,
and there aren't a lot
of designer products on the market.
Then you think
it's a good time to sell?
Provided interest rates
don't go any high...
Hi, Mel.
Don't let me interrupt.
No, I'm glad you're here.
I asked Jennifer to stop by,
take a look at the house.
I understand you want
to put the house up for sale.
I understand we were still
talking about it.
Jen figures we can make
at least $100,000.
More than enough for a down payment
on a couple of condos.
I have some clients who are dying
to be in the neighbourhood.
I could show it to them
before it's even listed.
That'd be great.
So, what do you think?
Yeah. Great.
When you're ready, just give me a
call, we'll start the ball rolling.
Will do.
And...see you tomorrow night.
The benefit.
Right.
Bye-bye.
'Bye.
So, you want to sell?
I was under the impression
we both did.
So, I say we stop talking about it
and get on with our lives.
Nice flowers.
Yeah.
I thought they'd...
brighten up the house.
44...
I don't know how
you can be so fucking heartless.
..45.
Have you had any idea
how hard this has been for him?
He's lost everything.
I can't help that.
You didn't have to fire him.
This is a business,
not a support group.
And its president...CEO,
whatever the fuck you call yourself,
happens to be gay.
So tell me - how can you cave
to such blatant homophobia?
Better yet, why don't I have
an expert explain?
Theodore. Would you step
into my office, please?
I bet you didn't even try
to fight for him, did you?
No, I did not.
You are unbelievable.
What's up, Bri?
Theodore.
How much do we stand to lose if
we lost the Brown Athletics account?
Ballpark figure?
That would be appropriate,
considering it's
a sporting goods company.
It's, um...a $20 million account.
And how much profit
does that generate for Kinnetic?
Say, roughly $2 million per annum.
Thank you.
You can chastise me all you want
for being heartless.
Doesn't cost me a cent.
But kindly explain to me why I should
sacrifice a $20 million account
just because your boyfriend suddenly
decides to announce he's queer.
I can see why
you're a successful businessman.
48...49...
So, you're back working the streets.
Thanks to you.
Are you coming?
Why in your wildest
homosexual fantasies
would you imagine
that I would attend such an event?
You gave Michael the club.
How could I say no
to my oldest and dearest friend?
And it is to protect the rights
of every gay person in the state.
Including yours.
Well, you'll to fight the good fight
without me.
I'll be tanning myself Down Under.
And perhaps a little on top.
You're going to Australia?
They say Mardi Gras in Sydney
is the gayest place on earth.
Except, of course, for Disneyland.
Well, take care of yourself.
You too.
So, everyone knows
the benefit's been moved.
Bunch of us were at the centre today,
making calls, sending emails.
Hi, baby!
You know...maybe we should
get Brian something.
What for?
If it weren't for him, we wouldn't
be having a benefit tonight.
I already thanked him. That's enough.
If you say so.
I do.
Hmm.
What's that for?
What's what for?
You say 'hmm' when you're thinking
something and don't want to say it.
Do I? Hmm.
I was just thinking it's a shame...
You can stop right there.
You don't even know
what I was going to say.
Surely it wasn't to remind me
of my appointment next Tuesday
to have my teeth cleaned.
Isn't it always the fucking way?
Kiki was supposed to relieve me an
hour ago. She still hasn't shown up.
Now I'm stuck with her shift.
That's ok. We'll wait for you.
Hey, Deb,
where's my chicken fricassee?
It's still fricking!
I want you boys to go. There's
no point in all of us missing it.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'll be there.
As soon as Kiki gets
her trannie ass here. I love you.
Deb! Order's up!
Are you alright?
In my Face Your Fear workshop,
they tell us to just keep breathing
steadily like this -
in...
In... ..and out.
It's also helpful
to have a partner coaching you.
Are you sure you didn't go
to Lamaze by mistake?
I sure hope we can find Mom in here.
I wouldn't worry.
If there's one person you can spot
in a crowd, it's your mother.
Hey, guys.
This is some event.
Think I might revisit the
halcyon days of my debauched youth
and dance till dawn.
If he makes it till 10:30,
it'll be a miracle.
Oh. Where's Brian?
I want to thank him.
He went to Australia for Mardi Gras.
Figures.
After all, he's slept with everyone
in this continent, so...
Oh, shit.
What's the matter?
My mother just arrived
with her boy toy.
It's so soap opera. So menopausal.
So humiliating.
Hello, darling. Mmm...
Somehow she seems
to perceive it differently.
You remember Tucker.
Ah. Hey.
Good to see you again.
How you doing?
Hi, Justin.
I'm going to get a drink.
Chardonnay, honey?
Perfect.
By the look on your face, I should
have ordered a sour apple martini.
Did you have to bring him?
Does he embarrass you?
Frankly, yes.
Well, when there's a Proposition 15
to take away the rights
of middle-aged women
to still have a life,
let's hope you show up for me.
May I have your attention, everyone?
Hi. I'm Emmett Honeycutt.
You may know me
as Channel 5's former Queer Guy.
But tonight I am still your queer Guy
and I want to welcome you
to this fabulous evening!
Guys, this is Lewis.
We met on husbandmaterial.com.
Oh! This sounds serious.
Michael and Ben got married
in Toronto last year.
You could be next!
..we can defeat Proposition 14!
Let's let the bigots
and the hatemongers
and the state capitol
and the White House know
we will not be silent!
Unless, of course, it's for
the silent auction.
So get those big bids in early.
And now...
I'm so excited. 1012
I'm so excited. 1013
It is my great honour and pleasure
to present our star attraction -
a girl who, like the rest of us,
just wants to have fun -
the one, the only Ms Cyndi Lauper!
Hey. Is my flight on time?
Yes, Mr Kinney.
If you didn't have to change
25 times...
The sitter was late. Don't blame me.
You've never been on time - not once.
You won't have to be bothered
with it much longer, will you?
Hey, girls.
Hi, Dusty.
I thought you weren't coming.
At the last minute, I said to Marie,
"It's too important."
"One of us has to be here." So I
came and she's home with the kids.
That's what I should've done.
Our new sitter was late.
You can always drop him at my place.
Let's go in.
Oh, shit.
What now?
My cell phone -
I must've left it in the car.
Christ.
You go in. I'll find you.
I'd better wait for Mel. You go.
Do you think I could get some water?
Michael, could you do me
a really big favour?
Lewis is kind of nervous in crowds
and I don't want to leave him.
Could you get him some water?
Uh, sure.
As long as you're going,
cranberry spritzer for me?
Hi!
Cranberry and soda and...
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck was that?
This just in from wdbx News -
there's been an explosion
at Babylon,
a local gay club, where a political
fundraiser was under way tonight.
Authorities fear there may be
many injuries, possibly fatalities.
They say there's no word yet as...
Turn around!
I want this whole area blocked off.
I want a clear path
for the ambulances.
Jennifer! Jennifer!
Jennifer!
Oh, my God.
Are you alright?
Justin's still in there.
You've got to find him.
We need you
to leave the building.
Everyone who is able,
please exit as quickly as possible!
Justin!
Everyone leave
as quickly as possible.
Ted! Ted?!
Ted! What the fuck happened?
I don't know.
Have you seen Justin?
He's not breathing!
Somebody help, please!
Oh, my God!
No! Oh, my God!
I need to get out of here.
Where's the door?
I can't find the door!
I've got a heavy bleeder
right over here.
Please!
The fucking thing is burning!
Help me!
Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
No. Just some scratches.
Have you seen my mother?
She's ok. She's outside.
She's looking for you.
There you are, baby.
My God, that was weird sex.
Have you seen Michael?!
Em?
Emmett!
Would you hurry, please?!
Deb, they're doing
the best they can.
I'm riding with him.
I'm his partner.
Get in. Get in. Hurry.
Get me to the hospital,
Karl, please.
I can't leave now. I'm on duty.
I'll get one of the boys
to take you.
I'll take you.
I knew I shouldn't have come.
You're going to be alright.
I've gotta get out of here.
Lewis. Lewis!
Wait!
Why'd I listen to you?!
Cardiac needle
and 500cc of adrenaline, stat.
Can I get a hand
with this, please?
Deb, why don't you sit down?
I tried that. Didn't work.
What...what if I lose him?
What am I going to do?
You won't lose him.
And this is not about you,
so sit down!
I'm sorry. You're right.
Well?
He's lost a lot of blood.
Before we can do anything,
he's going to need a transfusion.
What the fuck are you waiting for?
He's ab negative,
we're short on his type,
so we're checking all the hospitals.
ok. I'm O negative.
It's the universal donor, right?
Are you gay?
What's that got to do with anything?
We can't give blood because of hiv.
I don't have hiv.
It doesn't matter. Gays are
considered to be too high of a risk.
What about
all those straight studs and bitches
who fuck around
and don't use protection?
You'd take their blood, right?
It's an fda regulation.
Brian...
I don't give a shit!
Look... Take my blood, motherfucker!
Brian, Brian, Brian.
Brian, look, you couldn't give it
even if you were straight.
You've got cancer.
He's ok. He's ok.
He's right down there.
Sam Rawlings, Channel 7 News,
here with Drew Boyd.
Drew, having just come out
of the closet,
how do you feel about
what's happening here?
Are you concerned about losing
your fans now that you're gay?
Right now I'm more concerned
about people losing their lives!
Emmett?!
Are you ok?
Yeah. A little smoke inhalation.
I'll live.
I'm sorry I wasn't here.
Yeah, well...you're here now.
We've stabilised the blood loss,
but there's still internal bleeding
from a punctured spleen.
So we're going to need
to remove it immediately.
Will he be alright?
With this amount of blood loss,
uh...we can only hope for the best.
I'll give you a moment with him,
then we need to start prepping. ok?
You'd better fucking
come through this, you little shit.
I'm afraid I woke him.
But I just...needed to hold him.
He'll go back to sleep.
Are you...
What an idiotic question.
Of course you're not alright.
How could anyone be alright?
Just grateful.
Grateful that you're always late.
And that you forgot your cell phone.
Promise me you'll never be
on time for anything.
If you promise me
you'll never remember a thing.
I'll put him back in bed.
Linz?
Please?
As you know, I've always been
a good Catholic girl.
Even though, when it comes
to gays and abortion,
I think they're full of shit.
But still, I...
..I always believed
that God knew best
and there was a reason
for everything that he does.
But, um...
..this time I'm not so sure
why he let this happen
to Michael and the others.
So, this time I'm not asking him.
I'm telling him...to see
that Michael gets through this.
You notice I didn't say
"my son, Michael"?
Because it's not for me.
It's for him.
You want to say a prayer?
No.
But if you know
what's good for you...
..you'd better
fucking listen to her.
Do you mind if I tell people
Cyndi Lauper saved my life?
Nah, you do that.
My manager will love it.
Is Michael going to be ok?
They don't know.
When I heard what happened,
I tried to call you on your cell,
but...you didn't answer.
I was...so fucking scared.
All I could think was...
.."Please don't let anything
happen to him."
I love you.